SIMON MOR - FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Phone: +972 54 205 5028 Github: https://github.com/MagusM
Email: simomor@gmail.com
Website: https://simonmor.com

Professional Summary

8 years experienced Full Stack Developer & Technology Team Leader.

Managing projects from ideation to production.

Strong understanding of Agile methodologies and software development lifecycle

Technologies & Frameworks: JavaScript, React, Next.js, TypeScript, HTML+CSS, Node.js, Express.js, PHP, Docker, K8S, GCP, AWS, AZURE, restAPI,CI-CD, and SQL.

Technical Skills:

- Proficient in JavaScript, React, TypeScript, NodeJS, NextJS, PHP and SQL databases
- Experienced in working with AWS (Amazon Web Services), GCP (Google Cloud Platform) and Azure (Microsoft)
- Familiarity with GraphQL, Micro services architecture, Event driven and CI-CD

Work Experience

TEAM LEADER FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT - CarWiz Tel Aviv, ISRAEL | 2022 - Current

React, NextJS, Typescript, NodeJS, Postgres, GCP, GraphqL

- Led the development of CarWiz, successfully bringing it from a startup level to a stable and profitable product for the company
- Managed a team of 4 developers, established working methods with the team, and implemented Agile and sprints
- Successfully rebuilt the entire application infrastructure for CarWiz, including cloud infrastructure, DB, and other services, resulting in a more efficient and scalable

TEAM LEADER FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT- Matrix - Herzliya, ISRAEL | 2021 - 2022

NodeJS, React, TypeScript, Postgres, Azure, Graphql

- Led the development of the national application of epidemiology investigation used by the Israeli government and Health Department
- Managed a team, established working methods with the team, and implemented Agile and sprints
- Helped define project vision, short and long-term goals, and increased the quality of the service, bringing the application to be ready for even shelf product within months

TEAM LEADER FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT- Incredibuild – Tel Aviv, ISRAEL | 2019 – 2021

PHP. Laravel. NodeJS. React

- Managed 5 team members and led the technology development of the entire company site and store
- Owned the company site and store and led the redesign process of the company on the technology side
- Managed Agile, tasks, and priorities in the team on production deployment processes

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER- Wobi LTD - Tel Aviv, ISRAEL | 2017 - 2019

PHP, Laravel, NodeJs, React

- Built the company's main product server and client-side to support ongoing demand for client activities
- Refactored outdated, unscalable code into a modern app architecture
- Integrated Salesforce system as a CRM layer and refactored system services to work with it

SERVER DEVELOPER -Walla! News - Tel Aviv, ISRAEL | 2016 - 2017

Backend developer in Mail & Services Team | PHP

- Led and developed the Mail Application with constantly releasing new features and functionalities
- Engineered configuration server in PHP to provide the best mail service
- Built and maintained Open Source API and in-house "CASTLE" framework implementation
- In charge of data migration to CLOUD using Amazon Web Services

SERVER DEVELOPER - Wiser - TLV-San Francisco, US | 2015 - 2016

Backend developer in Legacy Team | PHP Yii framework

Education

- FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT WITH REACT & NODE COURSE Coursera & Hong Kong Uni 2019
- BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, CHEMICAL ENGINEERING –SCE collage of Engineering Ashdod, ISRAEL 2007-2013